<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ownershipDocument>

    <schemaVersion>X0609</schemaVersion>

    <documentType>4</documentType>

    <periodOfReport>2026-06-22</periodOfReport>

    <issuer>
        <issuerCik>0001824403</issuerCik>
        <issuerName>Reservoir Media, Inc.</issuerName>
        <issuerTradingSymbol>RSVR</issuerTradingSymbol>
        <issuerForeignTradingSymbol></issuerForeignTradingSymbol>
    </issuer>

    <reportingOwner>
        <reportingOwnerId>
            <rptOwnerCik>0001501578</rptOwnerCik>
            <rptOwnerName>Taylor Ryan P.</rptOwnerName>
        </reportingOwnerId>
        <reportingOwnerAddress>
            <rptOwnerNonUSAddressFlag>false</rptOwnerNonUSAddressFlag>
            <rptOwnerStreet1>C/O RESERVOIR MEDIA, INC.</rptOwnerStreet1>
            <rptOwnerStreet2>200 VARICK STREET, SUITE 801</rptOwnerStreet2>
            <rptOwnerCity>NEW YORK</rptOwnerCity>
            <rptOwnerState>NY</rptOwnerState>
            <rptOwnerZipCode>10014</rptOwnerZipCode>
            <rptOwnerStateDescription></rptOwnerStateDescription>
        </reportingOwnerAddress>
        <reportingOwnerRelationship>
            <isDirector>true</isDirector>
            <isOfficer>false</isOfficer>
            <isTenPercentOwner>false</isTenPercentOwner>
            <isOther>true</isOther>
            <otherText>May be deemed a 10% owner</otherText>
        </reportingOwnerRelationship>
    </reportingOwner>

    <aff10b5One>false</aff10b5One>

    <nonDerivativeTable>
        <nonDerivativeTransaction>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common stock, $0.0001 par value</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <transactionDate>
                <value>2026-06-22</value>
            </transactionDate>
            <transactionCoding>
                <transactionFormType>4</transactionFormType>
                <transactionCode>A</transactionCode>
                <equitySwapInvolved>false</equitySwapInvolved>
                <footnoteId id="F1"/>
            </transactionCoding>
            <transactionAmounts>
                <transactionShares>
                    <value>492</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F2"/>
                </transactionShares>
                <transactionPricePerShare>
                    <value>10.15</value>
                </transactionPricePerShare>
                <transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
                    <value>A</value>
                </transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
            </transactionAmounts>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>13595</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F3"/>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>D</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeTransaction>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common stock, $0.0001 par value</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>179389</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>By Richmond Hill Capital Partners, LP</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F4"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common stock, $0.0001 par value</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>13652372</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>By ER Reservoir, LLC</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F5"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F6"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
    </nonDerivativeTable>

    <footnotes>
        <footnote id="F1">Represents Deferred Stock Units (&quot;DSUs&quot;) awarded under the Reservoir Media, Inc. 2021 Omnibus Incentive Plan (the &quot;Plan&quot;). Each DSU is the economic equivalent of one share of common stock, $0.0001 par value per share (the &quot;Common Stock&quot;), of Reservoir Media, Inc. (the &quot;Issuer&quot;). The Reporting Person acquired these DSUs in connection with the Reporting Person's quarterly compensation for service as a non-employee director of the Issuer. The Reporting Person elected to receive payment of his quarterly compensation in DSUs in lieu of cash. This issuance of DSUs will be settled in shares of Common Stock on July 28, 2027 (the &quot;Settlement Date&quot;).  The Reporting Person disclaims beneficial ownership of the underlying shares except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F2">The number of DSUs received was calculated based on $10.15, which was the closing price of the Issuer's Common Stock on the date of grant.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F3">Represents Restricted Stock Units (&quot;RSUs&quot;) and DSUs awarded in connection with the Reporting Person's compensation for service as a non-employee director of the Issuer. Due to his position as the manager of the general partner of a manager of ER Reservoir LLC (the &quot;Fund&quot;), Reporting Person has directed the issuer to to transfer shares upon settlement of the RSUs and DSUs into the account of the Fund on the applicable Settlement Date. The Reporting Person disclaims beneficial ownership of the underlying shares except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F4">The amount of securities shown in this row is owned directly by Richmond Hill Capital Partners, LP (&quot;RHCP&quot;). The Reporting Person is the managing member of the general partner of RHCP and the manager of the general partner of Richmond Hill Investment Co., LP, the investment adviser to RHCP, and may be deemed to be a beneficial owner of the shares owned by RHCP. The Reporting Person disclaims any beneficial ownership of any of the Issuer's securities reported herein for purposes of Section 16 of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934, as amended (the &quot;Exchange Act&quot;) or otherwise, except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein, and the inclusion of the shares in this report shall not be deemed an admission of beneficial ownership of the reported shares for purposes of Section 16 of the Exchange Act, or for any other purpose.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F5">The amount of securities shown in this row is owned directly by the Fund. The Reporting Person is the manager of the general partner of a manager of the Fund and may be deemed to be a beneficial owner of the shares owned by the Fund. The amount of securities shown in this row also reflects a transfer of a total of 59,579 shares of Common Stock received upon the settlement of previously issued RSUs and DSUs that the Reporting Person directed to be transferred into the account of the Fund due to his position as the manager of the general partner of a manager of the Fund (Cont'd in FN 6)</footnote>
        <footnote id="F6">(Cont'd from FN 5) The Reporting Person disclaims any beneficial ownership of any of the Issuer's securities reported herein for purposes of Section 16 of the Exchange Act or otherwise, except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein, and the inclusion of the shares in this report shall not be deemed an admission of beneficial ownership of the reported shares for purposes of Section 16 of the Exchange Act, or for any other purpose. The amount of 418,576 shares of Common Stock owned directly by Essex Equity Joint Investment Vehicle, LLC previously reported on Form 4's by the Reporting Person have been removed from this and any subsequent Form 4's of the Reporting Person with respect to the Common Stock of the Issuer as such shares of Common Stock are no longer deemed to be beneficially owned by the Reporting Person.</footnote>
    </footnotes>

    <ownerSignature>
        <signatureName>/s/ James A. Heindlmeyer, as attorney-in-fact for Ryan P. Taylor</signatureName>
        <signatureDate>2026-06-24</signatureDate>
    </ownerSignature>
</ownershipDocument>
